
// Dedicated File explicitly for questions and answers for the code quiz game. For purposes of coding, answers[0] must ALWAYS be the correct answer to the question.

const quizQuestions = 
{questions:
    [
        {   
            number: "1",             
            question: "Which movie won best picture in 2017?", 
            answers: ["Moonlight", "La La Land", "Lion", "Hack Saw Ridge"],
        },
        {     
            number: "2",             
            question: "Who was the first woman to swim the English Channel?", 
            answers: ["Gertrude Ederle", "Amelia Gade Corson", "Mercedes Gleitze", "Hilda Sharp"],
        },
        {                
            number: "3",  
            question: "Which of these four actors guest starred on the TV show friends?", 
            answers: ["Sean Penn", "Ben Affleck", "Matt Damon", "Chris Pratt"],
        },
        {                
            number: "4",  
            question: "Which of these actors has played Batman?", 
            answers: ["Val Kilmer", "Billy Crudup", "Jared Leto", "Henry Cavill"],
        },
        {                
            number: "5",  
            question: "Who directed the 1958 movie Vertigo?", 
            answers: ["Alfred Hitchcock", "Orson Welles", "Frank Capra", "Fritz Lang"],
        },
        {                
            number: "6",  
            question: "Which of the following is NOT the name of a child of Kim Kardashian and Kanye West?", 
            answers: ["Reno", "Chicago", "Psalm", "Saint"],
        },
        {                
            number: "7",  
            question: "Which movie won the first official Best Picture Academy Award?", 
            answers: ["Wings", "The Jazz Singer", "Sunrise", "The Last Command"],
        },
        {                
            number: "8",  
            question: "What modern-day item made a cameo in the final season of Game of Thrones?", 
            answers: ["A Starbucks Cup", "A Camera", "A Can of Coca-Cola", "A pair of Nikes"],
        },
        {                
            number: "9",  
            question: "What is Chandler Bing’s middle name?", 
            answers: ["Muriel", "Madonna", "Mimsy", "Monica"],
        },
        {                
            number: "10",  
            question: "What are the names of the Sanderson sisters from Hocus Pocus?", 
            answers: ["Winifred, Mary and Sarah", "Winifred, Mary and Nancy", "Nancy, Mary and Sarah", "Winifred, Nancy and Sarah"],
        },
        {                
            number: "11",  
            question: "What is Rihanna’s real name?", 
            answers: ["Robyn Fenty", "Robin Fenty", "Robyn Alleyne", "Robin Alleyne"],
        },
        {                
            number: "12",  
            question: "What is Kramer’s first name on Seinfeld?", 
            answers: ["Cosmo", "Astro", "Sol", "Meteor"],
        },
        {                
            number: "13",  
            question: "What is the name of the news series John Krasinski launched during the coronavirus pandemic?", 
            answers: ["Some Good News", "The Silver Lining", "It Ain't All Bad", "Feel Good News"],
        },
        {                
            number: "14",  
            question: "Which tech entrepreneur named his son X Æ A-12?", 
            answers: ["Elon Musk", "Bill Gates", "Jeff Bezos", "Mark Zuckerberg"],
        },
        {                
            number: "15",  
            question: "What is the highest-grossing film of all time without taking inflation into account?", 
            answers: ["Avengers: Endgame", "Avatar", "Titanic", "Star Wars: The Force Awakens"],
        },
        {                
            number: "16",  
            question: "Which actor or actress is killed off in the opening scene of the movie Scream?", 
            answers: ["Drew Barrymore", "Courtney Cox", "Neve Campbell", "Rose McGowan"],
        },
        {                
            number: "17",  
            question: "Which film did Steven Spielberg win his first Oscar for Best Director?", 
            answers: ["Schindler's List", "Jaws", "E.T.", "Catch Me If You Can"],
        },
        {                
            number: "18",  
            question: "What is the name of Quint’s shark-hunting boat in Jaws?", 
            answers: ["The Orca", "The Whale", "The Dolphin", "The Shark"],
        },
        {                
            number: "19",  
            question: "What was the first feature-length animated film ever released?", 
            answers: ["Snow White", "Fantasia", "Pinocchio", "Dumbo"],
        },
        {                
            number: "20",  
            question: "What was the last movie Walt Disney was able to work on before he died?", 
            answers: ["The Jungle Book", "101 Dalmations", "The Sword in the Stone", "Mary Poppins"],
        },
    ]
};